(Sheldon:)Instead of being
weighed down by ambition,
(Sheldon:)you just float along
like a dead body in a river.
(Leonard:)I couldn't just
take the compliment.
(Leonard:)I had to ask why.
(Leonard:)You know, I do understand
what you're feeling.
(Leonard:)My brother and sister's
accomplishments
(Leonard:)have always been
held over my head.
(Sheldon:)How did you deal with it?
(Leonard:)I wet the bed until college,
but I don't think
(Leonard:)that's a quality fix.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe I was
surpassed by a geologist.
(Sheldon:)I mean...
rocks!
He studies rocks!
(Sheldon:)If rock is so great,
how come paper beats it?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I'm having
a primal urge
(Sheldon:)to throw this rock.
(Bernadette:)Do it.
(Leonard:)Visualize it
as your anger
a-and-and toss it
out of your life.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I will.